Guide to the Papers of Harrison Salisbury,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series III: Box Listing (unsorted)
  - Taraknath Das Foundation, 1965, 1967, 1968, 1970 (Box 29, 35, 40, 50)
  - Marshall B. Davidson (re Century), 1976 (Box 80)
  - Gordon Davies (Readers Digest), 1966 (Box 32)
  - Aubrey Davis (Martin Secker & Warburg), 1969 (Box 44)
  - Dolly Davis, 1961, 1962-63 (Box 18, 20)
  - James C. Davis, 1984 (Box 110)
  - Natasha Deakin, 1965 (Box 29)
  - Arthur H. Dean (CFR), 1966 (Box 32)
  - Joel Dean (re Century), 1969 (Box 44)
  - Vera Michaels Dean (Foreign Policy Assoc.), 1955, 1959, 1960 (Box 14, 16, 17)
  - Hugh Deane (US-China Peoples Friendship Assoc), 1988 (Box 120)
  - Martha Deane (Marian Young Taylor), 1958, 1966, 1967, 1969, 1971-73 (Box 15, 32, 36, 44, 55, 60, 65)
  - Emile de Antonio (Monday Film Production co), 1968 (Box 40)
  - William B. Decker (Dial Press), 1967 (Box 36)
  - Moshe Decter, 1962-63, 1964, 1970 (Box 20, 26, 50)
  - Stevan Dedijer, 1981 (Box 98)
  - Vladimir Dedijer, 1970-72, 1974, 1975, 1983 (Box 50, 55, 60, 72, 77, 106)
  - Jack Deegan (Newspaper Guild of NY), 1968-70 (Box 40, 44, 50)
  - Ernest De Filippis (re Aesthetic Realism), 1978-79 (Box 89)
  - Delacorte Press, 1981 (Box 98)
  - Demi, 1985, 1988, 1989, 1991, 1992 (Box 113, 120, 122, 127, 130)
  - Frank Dennis (USIA), 1958 (Box 15)
  - Andre Deutsch (pub), 1977, 1978-79 (Box 85, 89)
  - C. Robert Devine (Readers Digest), 1982 (Box 102)
  - Catherine E. Devlin ( Readers Digest), 1968 (Box 40)
  - Adreian Dewind (Natural Resources Defense Council), 1986, 1992 (Box 116, 130)
  - Dial Press, 1975, 1981, 1982 (Box 77, 98, 102)
  - Joan Dickinson (Mrs. William), 1973, 1981, 1982, 1990, 1991 (Box 65, 98, 102, 125, 127)
  - William Dickinson, 1962-7, 69, 76-9 (Box 20, 26, 29, 40, 44, 80, 85, 89)
  - John Diebold, 1970 (Box 50)
  - Digby Diehl, 1972, 74-5, 77-79 (Box 60, 72, 77, 85, 89)
  - Daniel Dietrich, 1987 (Box 118)
  - David Dietrich, 1990-91 (Box 125, 127)
  - Annie Dillard, 1986, 92 (Box 116, 130)
  - Douglas Dillon, 1975 (Box 77)
  - E. Grey Dimond, 1980-6, 88-90, 92-3, 93* (Box 94, 98, 102, 106, 110, 113, 116, 120, 122, 125, 130, 134, 137)
  - Mary Clark Dimond (Mrs. E. Grey), 1973-4, 80-2 (Box 65, 72, 94, 102)
  - Joseph C. Dine (Corporation for Public Broadcasting), 1970 (Box 50)
  - Tran Van Dinh (publications), 1992 (Box 130)
  - Dissent, 1986 (Box 116)
  - Farrell Dobbs, 1975-6 (Box 77, 80)
  - Byron Dobell (Esquire), 1965 (Box 29)
  - Francis Dobo (Arno Press), 1970-1 (Box 50, 55)
  - Gov. Ralph Docking (KS), 1974 (Box 72)
  - E. L. Doctorow (Dial Press), 1968 (Box 40)
  - Mrs. Allen R. Dodd (Saturday Review), 1962-3 (Box 20)
  - Sen. Christopher J. Dodd (CT), 1981, 83 (Box 98, 106)
  - Dodd, Mead, and Co. 1981 (Box 98)
  - John Dodds (Putnam's), 1971, 75 (Box 55, 77)
  - Cleveland E. Dodge, 1969 (Box 44)
  - Norton T. Dodge (Harvard Russian Research Center), 1954 (Box 14)
  - Robert Dodsworth (Mazomanie [WI] Historical Society), 1992 (Box 130)
  - Humphrey Doermann, 1975 (Box 77)
  - R. H. Doherty (Stravon Pub.), 1965-6 (Box 29, 32)
  - M. B. Dolinger (Chesapeake & Ohio RR), 1971 (Box 55)
  - Roger Donald (Little, Brown), 1975-6, 92-3 (Box 77, 80, 130, 134)
  - Hedley Donovan -- see Council on Foreign Relations, 1972 (Box 60)
  - Jerome Doolittle, 1982 (Box 102)
  - Doubleday, 1971-2, 74-81, 84-7 (Box 55, 60, 72, 77, 80, 85, 89, 94, 98, 110, 113, 116, 118)
  - Downhold Club, 1982 (Box 102)
  - Alice L. Downs, 1980 (Box 94)
  - Theodore Draper, 1965, 1981 (Box 29, 98)
  - Rep. Robert F. Drinan (re Sakharov), 1975 (Box 77)
  - Carol A. Driscoll (re Aesthetic Realism), 1980 (Box 94)
  - Alan Drury, 1973 (Box 65)
  - Orvile Dryfoos, 1958, 62-3 (Box 15, 20)
  - Susan W. Dryfoos, 1983, 93* (Box 106, 137)
  - Mel Dubin (Americans for Democratic Action), 1968 (Box 40)
  - Richard Dudman, 1989-90, 92 (Box 122, 125, 130)
  - Vera Dunham, 1981 (Box 98)
  - James N. Dunlop (World Press Institute), 1968-71 (Box 40, 44, 50, 55)
  - Louis Dupree, 1978-9 (Box 89)
  - Tillman Durdin, 1988 (Box 120)
  - Henry Durkin (Walker and Co.), 1970 (Box 50)
  - E. P. Dutton Co. 1958, 61, 73, 77, 80, 82 (Box 15, 18, 65, 85, 94, 102)
  - N. Dyakonov (Soviet Embassy), 1962-3 (Box 20)
  - Oscar Dystel (Bantam Books), 1964, 70-71 (Box 26, 50, 55)
  - James M. Eagan (Institute on Man and Science), 1969 (Box 45)
  - David Eames (Little, Brown), 1959 (Box 16)
  - Angela Earll (Sidgwick and Jackson), 1975 (Box 77)
  - P. D. East, 1960, 62-3, 67, 69 (Box 17, 20, 36, 45)
  - Mrs. P. D. East, 1972 (Box 60)
  - Eastern Europe Publications Exchange Fund, 1969-71, 82 (Box 45, 50, 55, 102)
  - Cyrus Eaton (office of, letters to), 1962-3, 68-70, 73, 77 (Box 20, 40, 45, 50, 65, 85)
  - Cyrus Eaton, Jr. 1974 (Box 72)
  - Richard Eberhart (Institute/Academy of Arts and Letters), 1980 (Box 94)
  - Abal Hassan Ebtehaj, 1962-7, 70, 75, 78-9, 83, 86 (Box 20, 26, 29, 32, 36, 50, 77, 89, 106, 116)
  - Alexander Eckstein, 1971 (Box 55)
  - Julius C. C. Edelstein (printed announcement), 1986 (Box 116)
  - Edgar Snow Memorial Fund, 1992 (Box 130)
  - Susan Edwards, 1991 (Box 127)
  - Daphne Ehrlich, 1971 (Box 55)
  - Paul Ehrlich, 1970 (Box 50)
  - Loren Eiseley (copy), 1975 (Box 77)
  - Carol Eitingen (Praeger), 1967 (Box 36)
  - Ivar Ekeland, 1970, 80, 88 (Box 50, 94, 120)
  - Sigurd Ekeland, 1971 (Box 55)
  - Yanne Ekeland, 1975 (Box 77)
  - The Elbe Alliance, 1986 (Box 116)
  - Julian Elfenbein, 1967 (Box 36)
  - Osborn Elliott, 1969-70 (Box 45, 50)
  - Sally Ellsworth (Mrs. Duncan), 1967, 75-7, 84, 93* (Box 36, 77, 81, 85, 110, 137)
  - Elodie Osborn, 1987 (Box 118)
  - T. Eric Embry, 1964 (Box 26)
  - Gloria Emerson, 1968, 70-1, 78-9, 85, 92, 93* (Box 40, 50, 55, 89, 113, 130, 137)
  - Encyclopaedia Britannica, 1962-5, 73, 83-4 (Box 20, 26, 29, 65, 106, 110)
  - Encyclopedia of New York City, 1991 (Box 127)
  - Judy Engelhardt (Knopf), 1967 (Box 36)
  - Tom Engelhardt (Pantheon), 1976, 81 (Box 81, 98)
  - Roger Enloe, 1962-3, 67 (Box 20, 36)
  - Jason Epstein, 1969 (Box 45)
  - Julius Epstein (Hoover Inst.), 1971 (Box 55)
  - Sonja Eriksson, 1978-80, 83-4, 87, 89 (Box 89, 94, 106, 110, 118, 122)
  - Morris Ernst (copies, office of), 1970-1 (Box 50, 55)
  - Ernst and Co. 1973 (Box 65)
  - John Ervin, Jr. 1964, 69, 74-6, 78-9, 88, 93* (Box 26, 45, 72, 77, 81, 89, 120, 137)
  - Esalen Institute, 1988, 90 (Box 120, 125)
  - John Espey, 1986, 90, 93 (Box 116, 125, 134)
  - John Willard Espy, 1993, 93* (Box 134, 137)
  - Esquire, 1974-5, 82 (Box 72, 77, 102)
  - John R. Everett, 1967-8, 71 (Box 36, 40, 55)
  - Everyman Opera, 1955, 58 (Box 14, 15)
  - Robert Evett (New Republic), 1965, 67 (Box 29, 36)
  - George W. Ewalt (re Agent Orange), 1983-5 (Box 106, 110, 113)
  - George Ewing (Canandaigua, NY), 1976-7 (Box 81, 85)
  - Eugene Exman, 1961 (Box 18)
  - Experiment in International Living, 1968 (Box 40)
  - Facts on File Publications, 1982 (Box 102)
  - Anne Fadiman, 1980-1 (Box 94, 98)
  - Merle Fainsod, 1964 (Box 26)
  - John King Fairbank, 1969, 71, 73-4, 77, 85, 87, 90, 92 (Box 45, 55, 65, 72, 85, 113, 118, 125, 130)
  - Wilma Fairbank (Mrs. John King), 1992, 1993* (Box 130, 137)
  - Richard Falk (Council on Foreign Relations), 1971 (Box 55)
  - Family Circle, 1972 (Box 60)
  - Family of Man, Society for the, 1968-9 (Box 40, 45)
  - Nathan Farb, 1981 (Box 98)
  - Barry Farber, 1987 (Box 118)
  - James Farley (Coca-Cola), 1960, 64 (Box 17, 26)
  - Farrar, Straus and Giroux, 1972-3 (Box 60, 65)
  - James T. Farrell, 1962-3, 65 (Box 20, 29)
  - William E. Farrrell (memorial), 1987 (Box 118)
  - David Farrer (Martin Secker and Warburg), 1966-8, 71-2, 74 (Box 32, 36, 40, 55, 60, 72)
  - Federation of American Scientists --see Harriette L. Phelps, Jeremy Stone, 1972 (Box 60)
  - Bernard T. Feld, 1969, 71 (Box 45, 55)
  - Bruce Felknor (Encyclopaedia Britannica), 1968, 70 (Box 40, 50)
  - Rep. Milicent Fenwick, 1976 (Box 81)
  - Anne Fessenden, 1989-91 (Box 122, 125, 127)
  - Arthur C. Fields, 1970-1 (Box 50, 55)
  - Marina Figner, 1967, 80-1, 84 (Box 36, 94, 98, 110)
  - Murray Findlay, 1974 (Box 72)
  - Sidney Fine (USIA ), 1955 (Box 14)
  - David Finkelstein (Ford Foundation), 1976 (Box 81)
  - Jack Finney, 1974 (Box 72)
  - Joachim Fiorillo (Society for the Family of Man), 1967 (Box 36)
  - S. Fischer Verlag, 1962-3, 69 (Box 20, 45)
  - Lydia Fish (re Vietnam Veterans folklore), 1983 (Box 107)
  - Leslie H. Fishel, Jr. (State Historical Society of WI), 1964-7, 69 (Box 26, 29, 32, 36, 45)
  - Anne-Louise Fisher (Andre Deutsch), 1978-9 (Box 89)
  - Dorothy Canfield Fisher (subject), 1993 (Box 134)
  - Ralph T. Fisher, Jr. 1962-3, 68, 82, 88 (Box 20, 40, 102, 120)
  - Roy Fisher, 1968, 73, 80-1 (Box 40, 65, 94, 98)
  - Jim Fitzpatrick, 1983 (Box 107)
  - Abram Flaxer (Wiltwyck School), 1969-70 (Box 45, 50)
  - James Fleming, 1969-71, 87, 91, 1993* (Box 45, 50, 55, 118, 127, 137)
  - Robert H. Fleming (White House), 1966 (Box 32)
  - Frederic Fleron, 1970 (Box 50)
  - Charles Bracelen Flood, 1971 (Box 55)
  - Fons, 1973 (Box 65)
  - Michael Foot, 1980-1 (Box 94, 98)
  - Malcolm Forbes, 1980 (Box 94)
  - Anne Ford (Houghton Mifflin), 1967 (Box 36)
  - Robert A. D. Ford, 1985-6, 88-9 (Box 113, 116, 120, 122)
  - Ford Foundation, 1978-9 (Box 90)
  - Foreign Affairs, 1973 (Box 65)
  - Foreign Policy, 1972 (Box 60)
  - Foreign Policy Association, 1958, 1973, 75 (Box 15, 65, 77)
  - Michael V. Forrestal, 1980 (Box 94)
  - Franklin S. Forsberg (Holt, Rinehart and Winston), 1970 (Box 50)
  - Arnold Forster, 1988 (Box 120)
  - Forum for US-Soviet Dialogue, 1980 (Box 94)
  - Lacey Fosburgh, 1980, 83-4. 91 (Box 94, 106, 110, 127)
  - Dorothy Fosdick (office of Sen. Henry Jackson), 1976 (Box 81)
  - Joseph M. Fox (Random House), 1968, 74, 76, 80, 84 (Box 40, 72, 81, 94, 110)
  - Melvin Frank, 1958, 62-3, 67-8, 71-3, 75-81, 83-4, 86, 88-90, 92, 93* (Box 15, 20, 36, 40, 55, 60, 65, 77, 81, 85, 90, 94, 98, 107, 110, 116, 120, 122, 125, 130, 137)
  - Charles Frankel, 1974 (Box 72)
  - Max Frankel (letters to, copies), 1968, 70, 81 (Box 40, 50, 98)
  - Helen Frankenthaler (brochures), 1977-9, 81 (Box 85, 90, 98)
  - Noble Frankland, 1973, 76 (Box 65, 81)
  - Franklin Library, 1976, 78-9, 82-3, 85-90 (Box 81, 90, 102, 107, 113, 116, 118, 120, 122, 125)
  - George S. Franklin, Jr. 1967-71 (Box 36, 40, 45, 50, 55)
  - Anne Freedgood (Doubleday, Random House), 1967, 1983 (Box 36, 107)
  - Emmanuel R. Freedman, 1959, 71 (Box 16, 55)
  - Freedom Forum, 1993 (Box 134)
  - Freedom House, 1960 (Box 17)
  - Edward L. Freers, 1958 (Box 15)
  - Eliot Fremont-Smith, 1962-3, 69-70, 72 (Box 20, 45, 50, 60)
  - Gerald Freund (Rockefeller Foundation), 1961 (Box 18)
  - Russell Fridley (Minn. Historical Society), 1977 (Box 85)
  - Friedburg (Judd Teller), 1970 (Box 50)
  - Bea Friedland, 1980-2, 84 (Box 94, 98, 102, 110)
  - Thomas L. Friedman (New York Times), 1983 (Box 107)
  - Alfred Friendly, 1962-3 (Box 20)
  - Friends of Sikkim, 1975 (Box 77)
  - Friendship Ambassadors, Inc, 1976 (Box 81)
  - R. Buckminster Fuller (letter to, copies), 1970-1, 75, 83 (Box 50, 55, 77, 107)
  - Fund for Peace, 1972-3 (Box 60, 65)
  - Fund for Education in World Order, 1968 (Box 40)
  - Funk and Wagnalls, 1956-8, 60-1, 69, 72, 75, 77 (Box 14, 15, 17, 18, 44, 60, 77, 85)
  - Alexander Fursenko, 1968, 71, 74-6, 78-80, 92, 93* (Box 40, 55, 72, 77, 81, 90, 94, 130, 137)
  - Gary Gach, 1992-3 (Box 130, 134)
  - John Lewis Gaddis, 1987-88 (Box 118, 120)
  - William Gaddis, 1993* (Box 138)
  - Mary Anne Gaetti, 1980 (Box 95)
  - Lewis Galantiere, 1965 (Box 30)
  - John Kenneth Galbraith (copy), 1971 (Box 55)
  - Gale Research Co. (Contemporary Authors Autobigraphy), 1986, 89 (Box 116, 122)
  - Wes Gallagher, 1967 (Box 36)
  - Roland Gammon, 1960, 68-9 (Box 17, 41, 45)
  - Roland Gant, 1959-60, 62-3 (Box 16, 17, 20)
  - W. Horseley Gantt Papers, 1987 (Box 118)
  - Oscar Garcia-Rivera, 1981, 89-93, 93* (Box 99, 122, 125, 127, 130, 134, 138)
  - John W. Gardner, 1974 (Box 72)
  - Lloyd Garrison, 1978-9 (Box 90)
  - David Garst, 1978-80, 82, 89-92 (Box 90, 95, 103, 122, 125, 127, 130)
  - Roswell Garst, 1960, 62-6, 69-70, 73 (Box 17, 20, 26, 30, 32, 45, 50, 65)
  - Richard L. Garwin (IBM), 1978-9, 84 (Box 90, 110)
  - The Gates of Hell (subject), 1976 (Box 81)
  - Wilson Gathings, 1976 (Box 81)
  - Bernard Geis, 1964-5, 72-5, 78-9, 81-3, 86-8 (Box 26, 30, 60, 65, 72, 77, 90, 99, 103, 107, 116, 118, 120)
  - Darlene Geis, 1959-61, 72, 80, 84 (Box 16, 17, 18, 60, 95, 110)
  - Maxwell Geismar, 1966 (Box 32)
  - Arthur Gelb, 1976, 84 (Box 81, 110)
  - Lionel Gelber Prize, 1992 (Box 130)
  - John T. Geoghegan (Coward-McCann), 1967-8, 76 (Box 36, 41, 81)
  - Barbara M. Geraghty (Doubleday), 1971 (Box 55)
  - Eugene Gervasi (Knopf), 1964 (Box 26)
  - Henri Ghent, 1968 (Box 41)
  - Mary Bass Gibson, 1972 (Box 60)
  - K. Dun Gifford, 1983 (Box 107)
  - Martin Gilbert, 1989 (Box 122)
  - Brendan Gill (letter to, re Century), 1968, 75 (Box 41, 77)
  - Gene Gillette, 1962-4, 69-70 (Box 20, 26, 45, 50)
  - Kenneth S. Giniger, 1964-5, 67, 69-70, 82, 84, 93* (Box 26, 30, 36, 45, 50, 103, 110, 138)
  - Allen Ginsberg (letters to, copies), 1968-9, 81 (Box 41, 45, 99)
  - Alexander Ginsburg Defense Committee, 1978-9 (Box 90)
  - GIRO (Global Issues Resource Org.), 1983 (Box 107)
  - Rochelle Girson (Saturday Review), 1962-4, 66 (Box 20, 26, 32)
  - Edmund Glass, 1980 (Box 95)
  - (Sir) Leslie Glass, 1976, 80, 83-4 (Box 81, 95, 107, 110)
  - Ira Glasser (ACLU), 1984 (Box 110)
  - Sidney Glazier, 1974, 77-9, 82 (Box 72, 85, 90, 103)
  - John B. Goetz (University of Chicago Press), 1962-3 (Box 20,)
  - Philip W. Goetz (Encyclopaedia Britannica), 1964 (Box 26)
  - Tom Goetz, 1964-5 (Box 26, 30)
  - Joseph gold (American Cancer Society), 1988 (Box 120)
  - Carol Goldberg (Anchor Books, Doubleday), 1971 (Box 55)
  - Arthur S. Golden, 1980-2, 84, 93* (Box 95, 99, 103, 110, 138)
  - Ben Hale Golden, 1962-3 (Box 20)
  - Ruth Sulzberger Golden (Mrs. Ben Hale), 1966-8 (Box 32, 36, 41)
  - Trudy Golden (Mrs. Arthur S.), 1989 (Box 122)
  - William T. Golden, 1983 (Box 107)
  - Robert M. Goldenson (Book-of-the-Month Club), 1965 (Box 30)
  - Howard Goldfinger, 1964-5, 67 (Box 26, 30, 36)
  - Marshall Goldman, 1976 (Box 81)
  - Michel Gordey, 1959, 62-4, 67-74, 76-9, 90-92, 93* (Box 16, 20, 26, 36, 41, 45, 50, 55, 60, 66, 72, 81, 85, 90, 125, 127, 130, 138)
  - Dorothy Gordon, 1962-3 (Box 20)
  - Jesse Gordon (The Nation), 1967-9 (Box 36, 41, 45)
  - Max Gordon, 1966, 70-1, 73-4, 80 (Box 32, 50, 55, 66, 72, 95)
  - Milton Gordon, 1972, 76, 78-9, 82, 89 (Box 60, 81, 90, 103, 122)
  - Ruth Gordon, 1991 (Box 127)
  - Jesse Gorkin (Parade), 1975 (Box 77)
  - Howard Gotlieb, 1964, 67-70, 76, 90, 92 (Box 26, 36, 41, 45, 50, 81, 125, 130)
  - Robert Gottlieb, 1989 (Box 122)
  - Sanford Gottlieb (SANE), 1962-3 (Box 20)
  - Roman Goul, 1962-4 (Box 20, 26)
  - Paul Grabbe, 1978-9 (Box 90)
  - Robert D. Graff, 1962-3, 65, 67 (Box 20, 30, 36)
  - Gordon Graham (Students for Democratic Action), 1958 (Box 15)
  - Beatrice Grant, 1962-4 (Box 20, 26)
  - Cleve Gray, 1969 (Box 45)
  - Francine du Plessix Gray (envelope, clipping), 1981 (Box 99)
  - GREAT SOVIET ENCYCLOPEDIA (subject), 1976 (Box 81)
  - Ashbel Green, 1971, 74-6, 78-9 (Box 55, 72, 77, 81, 90)
  - Dan Green, 1964 (Box 26)
  - Roy Green (Atlantic Monthly), 1965 (Box 30)
  - Tom Green and Terry Pearce, 1986, 92 (Box 116, 130)
  - Dorothea S. Greenbaum (Mrs. Edward), 1981 (Box 99)
  - Edward S. Greenbaum, 1967, 70 (Box 36, 50)
  - Vartan Gregorian (New York Public Library), 1984 (Box 110)
  - Don Grierson (re Herbert Matthews), 1986 (Box 116)
  - Kenneth N. Grigg, 1981 (Box 99)
  - Grolier Society, 1955, 59-65, 78-9 (Box 14, 16, 17, 18, 20, 26, 30, 90)
  - Peter Grose (New York Times), 1968-69, 71 (Box 41, 45, 55)
  - Ernest A. Gross, 1978-9, 93* (Box 90, 138)
  - Gerald Gross (Pantheon), 1962-3 (Box 20)
  - Grove Press, 1967 (Box 36)
  - Anne M. Gruber (American Committee on US-Sov. Relations), 1986 (Box 116)
  - Leo Gruliow (CDSP), 1955, 59, 65-7, 69, 71, 74, 87, 91, 93* (Box 14, 16, 30, 32, 36, 45, 55, 72, 118, 127, 138)
  - Samuel Gruper (Macarthur Fellowship Program), 1988, 92 (Box 120, 130)
  - Flora Lewis (Gruson), 1972 (Box 60)
  - Sydney Gruson, 1968, 71, 73-4, 77-9, 81, 91 (Box 41, 55, 66, 72, 85, 90, 99, 127)
  - Robert C. Guccione, 1993 (Box 134)
  - Guggenheim Foundation, 1972, 75-7, 80-1, 83, 87, 92 (Box 60, 77, 81, 85, 95, 99, 107, 118, 130)
  - Newspaper Guild contract (memos, etc.), 1965 (Box 30)
  - Polly Guinther (Putnam's), 1962-3 (Box 20)
  - Jane Gunther (Mrs. John), 1993* (Box 138)
  - Greg Guroff (USIA), 1992 (Box 130)
  - William Guthrie (Little, Brown), 1975 (Box 77)
  - Clyde Haberman, 1993* (Box 138)
  - Jeremy Hadfield (Martin Secker and Warburg), 1967 (Box 36)
  - Beulah Hagen, 1964 (Box 26)
  - James Hagerty, 1960 (Box 17)
  - Edith Haggard, 1973, 1993* (Box 66, 138)
  - Michael L. Haider (Family of Man dinner), 1966 (Box 33)
  - Najeeb E. Halaby (National Committee on US-China Relations), 1969 (Box 45)
  - David Halberstam (letters to, copy), 1968-9, 83, 86-7 (Box 41, 45, 107, 116, 118)
  - Helen Hall, 1959 (Box 16)
  - Mary Harrington Hall (Psychology Today), 1967-9 (Box 36, 41, 45)
  - Roger Halle, 1991-2 (Box 128, 131)
  - W. D. Halsey -- see Macmillan and Co., 1973 (Box 66)
  - Charles V. Hamilton, 1968 (Box 41)
  - Jane Hamilton-Merritt, 1971-80, 82-6, 90-91 (Box 55, 60, 66, 72, 77, 81, 85, 90, 95, 103, 107, 111, 114, 116, 125, 128)
  - Edna Hammond and Paula Schwarz, 1983 (Box 107)
  - Oliver W. Hammonds, 1986 (Box 116)
  - Han Suyin, 1968-72, 77, 87 (Box 41, 45, 50, 55, 60, 85, 118)
  - Meyer Handler, 1964, 67 (Box 26, 36)
  - Wynn Handman (American Place Theater), 1966-7 (Box 33, 36)
  - John Hangin (Mongolia Society), 1962-3, 67, 69, 71, 78-9, 89 (Box 21, 36, 45, 55, 90, 122)
  - Robert Hansen, 1977 (Box 85)
  - Harcourt Brace Jovanovich/ and World, 1972-4 (Box 60, 66, 72)
  - Elizabeth Hardwick, 1978-9, 92, 93* (Box 90, 131, 138)
  - Hugh Hardy (re American Academy/ Institute), 1992 (Box 131)
  - C. J. Harkrader, 1964-70 (Box 26, 30, 33, 36, 41, 45, 50)
  - Harper and Brothers (Harper and Row), 1955, 58, 60-3, 65-6, 68-85, 88 (Box 14, 15, 17, 18, 21, 30, 33, 41, 45, 50, 55, 60, 66, 72, 77, 81, 85, 90, 95, 99, 103, 107, 111, 114, 120)
  - Averell Harriman (letter to), 1968 (Box 41)
  - Averell Harriman(invitation), 1981 (Box 99)
  - Averell Harriman(office of), 1984 (Box 111)
  - Harriman Institute, 1982 (Box 103)
  - Leonard Harris (Encyclopaedia Britannica), 1965, 68 (Box 30, 41)
  - Lou Harris, 1967 (Box 36)
  - Stuart Harris (Harper and Row), 1964 (Box 26)
  - J. Fraser Harrison (Sidgwick and Jackson), 1975 (Box 77)
  - Selig Harrison, 1977-9 (Box 85, 90)
  - David C. Harrop (Doubleday), 1976 (Box 81)
  - John L. Hart, 1982-3 (Box 103, 107)
  - Catherine Hartman, 1964-5, 67 (Box 26, 30, 36)
  - David Hartman, 1982-3 (Box 103, 107)
  - Joyce Hartman, 1968 (Box 41)
  - Harvard, 1980-2, 87 (Box 95, 99, 103, 118)
  - Board of Overseers --re Visiting Committees, 1966, 69-79 (Box 33, 45, 50, 55, 60, 66, 72, 77, 81, 85, 90)
  - Nieman Foundation, 1974 (Box 73)
  - Russian Research Center, 1975, 84 (Box 78, 111)
  - George C. Haselton, 1970 (Box 50)
  - Thomas G. Haseman (Buhler, King, & Buhler), 1968 (Box 41)
  - Riyad Hashem (Minister of Justice, Jordan), 1967 (Box 36)
  - Alfred Hasler (copy of Tom Wicker letter), 1970 (Box 50)
  - Peter Hastings, 1967 (Box 36)
  - Joan Haverly, 1971 (Box 55)
  - Tom Hayden, 1967, 88 (Box 36, 120)
  - Harold Hayes (Esquire), 1969 (Box 45)
  - Samuel P. Hayes, 1967, 69-70 (Box 36, 45, 50)
  - Tim Hays, 1983 (Box 107)
  - John Hazard, 1969 (Box 45)
  - James A. Healy (NYSE), 1966 (Box 33)
  - Rex Hearn (Harper's), 1966 (Box 33)
  - Harold Hecht, 1959-60 (Box 16, 17)
  - Barbara Heckethorn (Macmillan and Co.), 1965 (Box 30)
  - Tom Hedley (Esquire), 1969 (Box 45)
  - Per Egil Hegge, 1971, 73 (Box 55, 66)
  - Peter Heggie, 1964-6 (Box 26, 30, 33)
  - Robert Heilbroner -- see Century, 1983 (Box 107)
  - Hans Heinemann, 1958-9, 62-6 (Box 15, 16, 21, 26, 30, 33)
  - Piltti Heiskanen, 1974-9, 82, 92 (Box 72, 77, 81, 85, 90, 103, 131)
  - Andrew Heiskell, 1981, 93* (Box 99, 138)
  - Marian Sulzberger Heiskell (Mrs. Andrew), 1975, 78-9, 93* (Box 77, 90, 138)
  - Betty Heller, 1977 (Box 85)
  - Walter Heller (Council of Economic Advisors), 1962-3 (Box 21)
  - Helsinki Watch, 1980 (Box 95)
  - William Henderson (Funk and Wagnalls), 1970-1 (Box 50, 55)
  - John Hersey (letter to), 1985 (Box 114)
  - John Hersey(subject -- obituary, etc.), 1993 (Box 134)
  - James Heslin (re Century), 1974 (Box 72)
  - Katrina vanden Heuvel, 1990 (Box 125)
  - W. R. Higginbotham, 1966, 71, 81-2, 84, 86-8 (Box 33, 55, 99, 103, 111, 116, 118, 120)
  - Jean Highland, 1970, 78-9, 86, 88-9 (Box 50, 90, 116, 120, 122)
  - Hugo John Hildebrandt, 1981-3 (Box 99, 103, 107)
  - Carol Hill (Pantheon), 1967 (Box 36)
  - Gladwin Hill (New York Times), 1968 (Box 41)
  - Sidney Hillman Foundation, 1969, 71-3, 77, 84-5, 87, 92-3 (Box 45, 55, 60, 66, 85, 111, 114, 118, 131, 134)
  - Roger Hilsman (National Committee on US-China Relations), 1968 (Box 41)
  - Peter Hillyer, 1966 (Box 33)
  - Ronald Hilton, 1982 (Box 103)
  - Robert Himmer, 1989 (Box 122)
  - Harold C. Hinton, 1958 (Box 15)
  - William Hinton (US-China Peoples Friendship Assoc.), 1973 (Box 66)
  - David Hirshey (Esquire), 1992 (Box 131)
  - Demi Hitz, 1990 (Box 125)
  - John Hlavacek, 1964, 89 (Box 26, 122)
  - Peggy Hlavacek (Mrs. John), 1958, 66, 78-9 (Box 15, 33, 90)
  - Ho Chi Minh (subject), 1971 (Box 55)
  - Adam Hochschild, 1976, 81-3, 86, 88, 92, 93* (Box 81, 99, 103, 107, 116, 120, 131, 138)
  - Harold K. Hochschild, 1970, 72-3, 76-81 (Box 50, 60, 66, 81, 85, 90, 95, 99)
  - James Hoge, 1987 (Box 118)
  - John Hohenberg (Pulitzer prizes), 1960, 64, 66-70, 73, 75 (Box 17, 26, 33, 36, 41, 45, 50, 66, 77)
  - Richard Holbrooke (Foreign Affairs), 1971 (Box 55)
  - Arthur C. Holden, 1989, 92 (Box 122, 131)
  - Isabel Holland (Putnam's), 1968 (Box 41)
  - Kenneth Holland (Institute of International Education), 1960, 70 (Box 17, 50)
  - Richard Holland (Farrar, Straus and Giroux), 1967 (Box 36)
  - Don Hollenbeck Awards, 1975 (Box 77)
  - Everett Holles (General Atomic), 1962-5, 67 (Box 21, 26, 30, 36)
  - Bill Holm, 1987, 89, 91-3, 93* (Box 118, 122, 127, 131, 134, 138)
  - Ruth Sulzberger Holmberg, 1973, 77-81, 83, 93* (Box 66, 85, 90, 95, 99, 107, 138)
  - Holt, Rinehart and Winston, 1972, 77-9, 81-5 (Box 60, 86, 90, 99, 103, 107, 111, 114)
  - Bob Hood, 1962-3 (Box 21)
  - John J. Hoodack (Nativity Mission Center), 1958, 62-3, 66-7, 70 (Box 15, 21, 33, 36, 50)
  - Townsend Hoopes, 1973, 76, 86 (Box 66, 81, 116)
  - Helen Hoover, 1964-9, 73-4 (Box 26, 30, 33, 36, 41, 45, 66, 72)
  - J. Edgar Hoover (subject), 1971 (Box 55)
  - Hoover Institution, 1978-9, 83 (Box 90, 107)
  - Gene Hopster, 1967, 74-5, 84, 92 (Box 36, 72, 77, 111, 131)
  - Edward C. Horman, 1978-9 (Box 90)
  - Irving Louis Horowitz, 1980-1, 83, 93* (Box 95, 99, 107, 138)
  - James R. Houghton (Corning Glass, re Fairbank Center, Harvard), 1987 (Box 118)
  - Houghton Mifflin, 1962-3, 66, 71-4, 76, 78-9 (Box 21, 33, 55, 60, 66, 72, 81, 90)
  - Walter Hoving, 1962-3 (Box 21)
  - Howard County Council (Experiment in International Living), 1974 (Box 72)
  - Irving Howe, 1972 (Box 60)
  - John Howe (Encyclopaedia Britannica), 1962-3, 66 (Box 21, 33)
  - Quincy Howe, 1968, 1972, 76 (Box 41, 60, 81)
  - Douglass Morse Howell, 1987-9 (Box 118, 120, 122)
  - Carol Howland (Mademoiselle), 1965 (Box 30)
  - Ken Hsu, 1981-2 (Box 99, 103)
  - Ray Huang, 1982, 85, 87-8 (Box 103, 114, 118, 120)
  - Linda Hubbard (Modern Maturity), 1986, 92 (Box 116, 131)
  - Richard Hudson, 1974-5, 89, 93* (Box 72, 77, 122, 138)
  - Sen. Harold E. Hughes, 1970-1 (Box 50, 55)
  - Lawrence Hughes (William Morrow), 1964-5 (Box 26, 30)